Hoenn Rangers Coexistence Force
	TV Mauville created the Hoenn Rangers Coexistence Force (Japanese: 共存戦隊ホウエンジャー Hoenn Rangers Coexistence Squadron), a team of action heroes that were overshadowed by the emergence of Pokémon Contest Spectaculars. Hoenn TV has been renamed to TV Mauville (Japanese: テレビキンセツ TV Kinsetsu)
	Telemauv (Japanese: テレキンちゃん Telekin-chan) is the station's mascot, a television shaped like Mauville city with eyes, arms, and legs. "We fight for the peaceful coexistence of Pokémon, nature, and people!"
	
	Littleroot Crimson - Brave but laid-back hero. (Red) [Slateport City Market Toy Box]
	Mauville Yellow - Powerful yet absentminded hero. (Yellow) [TV Mauville Toy Shelf]
	Rustboro Ivory - A sensitive and smart heroine. (White) [Weather Institute Toy Shelf]
	Fallarbor Bordeaux - Quick-moving but pessimistic hero. (Black) [Lilycove Department Store Toy Shelf]
	Lilycove Viridian - Heroine able to fly through the sky - yet suffers a fear of heights. (Green) [Lilycove Department Store Rooftop] Carvanha or Prinplup motif costume?
	Pacifidlog Cobalt - A self-conscious but cool heroine. (Blue) [Mossdeep City Space Center Toy Shelf]
